[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What is 2*2?",
    "answerArr": [1, 2, 3, 4],
    "subject": "math",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "Find the One word with the Long a sound",
    "answerArr": ["bone", "base", "tried", "cap"],
    "subject": "english",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "I ___ good at climbing trees",
    "answerArr": ["am", "is", "are", "was"],
    "subject": "english",
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "I have to ___ my homework.",
    "answerArr": ["does", "do", "done", "did"],
    "subject": "english",
    "answer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Find a rhyming word for SEA",
    "answerArr": ["Key", "Say", "cram", "ya"],
    "subject": "english",
    "answer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What are Nouns?",
    "answerArr": [
      "Names actions",
      "Substitute other nouns",
      "Describe actions",
      "Name people, animals, places, events, and things"
    ],
    "subject": "english",
    "answer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "What is the plural form of Banana?",
    "answerArr": ["Bananas", "Bananae", "Banana", "Bananaes"],
    "subject": "english",
    "answer": 0
  },

  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "______ comes just before 413.",
    "answerArr": ["403", "412", "410", "414"],
    "subject": "math",
    "answer": 1
  },

  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "In 289, the place value of 8 is____________.",
    "answerArr": ["Ones", "Hundreds", "Tens", "Thousands"],
    "subject": "math",
    "answer": 2
  },

  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "232, 242, ____ , 262. The missing number in the pattern is ____.",
    "answerArr": ["222", "225", "252", "243"],
    "subject": "math",
    "answer": 2
  },

  {
    "id": 11,
    "question": "10+43+34=____",
    "answerArr": ["87", "77", "104334", "197"],
    "subject": "math",
    "answer": 0
  }
]
